SEBASTIAN ENCISO

Full Stack Developer

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Hard-working Computer Science major (3.4 GPA) California State University-Northridge graduate, with 11.5+ years of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of programming skills to successfully fill the Software Engineering Internship role at your company. Frequently praised as focused by my peers, I can be relied upon to assist your company achieve its optimum goals.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TRANSPORTER

Providence Saint Josephs Hospital, Burbank, CA / Feb 2017 - Present

- Respond to emergency situations with calmness and logical practices in handling patients who are scared, hysterical or in need of reassurance.
- Transport patients to treatment units, testing units, operating rooms, or other areas using wheelchairs, stretchers, or moveable beds.
- Transport specimens, laboratory items, or pharmacy items, ensuring proper documentation and delivery to authorized personnel.
- Work with bedridden patients, to ensure a sanitary and safe hospital stay.
- Proficient in Epic Software for hospital documentation
- Collaborate with doctors, surgeons, and nurses to ensure patients safe transport

PEPPERIDGE FARM DRIVER

Pepperidge Farm, Irwindale, CA / Aug 2015 - Dec 2017

- Listen and resolve customers' complaints regarding products or services.
- Inform customers of new products or services and price changes.
- Prepare customer orders and sales contracts
- Document sales or delivery information on daily records.
- Arrange displays and merchandise pertaining to sales promotions
- Distribute sales promotion materials to customers.

- Sebastianbabble@gmail.com
- (818) 640-4479
- 3632 Fairesta St.
 La Crescenta, CA, 91214
- github.com/Sebastianbabble

EDUCATION

CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY-NORTHRIDGE GPA: 3.4

Northridge, CA

B.S. Computer Science

Relevant Coursework

- Advanced Data Structures
- Introduction to Software Engineering
- Concepts of Programming Languages
- Computer Organization
- Web development

Awards & Honors

 The National Society of Leadership and Success

Extracurricular Activities

- Layer 8 Computer Security Club
- Artificial Intelligence Association

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Proficient in Javascript, CSS, C#, C++, ASP.NET, React, Python

LIFEGUARD

YMCA, Tujunga, CA / Jan 2009 – May 2012

- Examine injured persons and administer first aid or cardiopulmonary resuscitation, if necessary, using training and medical supplies and equipment.
- Contact emergency medical personnel in case of serious injury.
- Complete and maintain records of weather and beach conditions, emergency medical treatments performed, and other relevant incident information.
- Maintain quality of pool water by testing chemical levels.
- Provide assistance with staff selection, training, and supervision.

Ability to work well alone or with others

Team-oriented quality Strong Work Ethic Self-motivated Adaptability in decision-making

Strategic and logical thinker